Kheel Center Office Files /4088
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Office Files
1947-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Labor-Management Documentation Center (LMDC)
Kheel Center
/4088
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
7980472
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 30, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4049: Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4051: Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4072: Kheel Center Additional Files /4074: Kheel Center Additional Office Files, User Applications /4090: Kheel Center R. Strassberg Conservation Files /4141: Kheel Center Additional Administrative Files
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Martin P. Catherwood Library; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
7980472
- Miscellaneous Correspondence Beginning with A, 1966-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1951-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Society of American Archivists, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Society of American Archivists, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Society of American Archivists, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Society of American Archivists. Building and Technical Processes Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Society of American Archivists. Professional Organizations. Building and Technical Processes Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Society of American Archivists. Conservation Professional Affinity Group, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Society of American Archivists, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- American Institute for Conservation of Historic and Artistic Works, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Folder B, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Folder C, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Public Archives of Canada, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Baltimore Regional Joint Board, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Clothing and Textile Workers Union Amalgamated. Chicago Joint Board, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Laundry Workers Department, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  May 13 1981
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. New England Joint Board, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  July 30 1979 - April 24 1981
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. New York Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Potofsky Family, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Report to National Historical Publications and Records Commission to Survey the Record Situation of those Railroads Absorbed into the Conrail (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cornell University Memos, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- CUL Ad Hoc Task Force on Conservation. Calendar and Staff Directory, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- CUL Ad Hoc Task Force on Conservation. Interview Questions, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- CUL Ad-Hoc Task Force on Conservation. Letters Sent Out (Box 1, Folder 24)
- CUL Conservation Committee. Mailing Labels (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cornell University Libraries. Academic Assembly Steering Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Academic Assembly Steering Committee. Docketed Documents, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Cornell University Libraries. Academic Assembly Steering Committee Docket. Supporting Documents, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  May 21 1979
- Cornell University Libraries. Ballots, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  April and July 1978
- Cornell University Libraries. Grants, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  November 4 and 6 1980
- Cornell University Libraries. Memos, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Cornell University Libraries. Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Cornell University Libraries. Memos, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Cornell University Libraries. Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cornell University Libraries. Memos, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Cornell University Libraries. New York Historical Resources Project Preliminary Program Statement, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Cornell University Libraries. Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  November and December 1977. April 1979
- CUL Safety, Emergencies and Disasters Committee. Mailing Labels (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Cornell University Libraries. Steering Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Folder D, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Folder E, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Folder F, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Folder G, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Folder H, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Folder I, 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  French and English
- ILR Catherwood Library. Memos, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ILR Catherwood Library. Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ILR Catherwood Library. Memos, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILR School. Memos, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ILR School. Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ILR School. Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ILR School. Memos, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Folder J, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  January 5 1982 - May 3 1984
- Folder K, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Folder L, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Library of Congress, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Folder M, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Archives and Libraries. University of Michigan, 1978-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Microfilming Corporation of America, 1973-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Folder N, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- US National Archives and Records Service, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- New York State Historical Resources Center, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- New York State Archives, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- New York State Studies Group Newsletter, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  February 1978
- Florence Nixon, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Northeast Document Conservation Center, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Folder O, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Folder P, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  English and French
- Folder Q (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Folder R, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Research Libraries Group. RLIN, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Research Libraries Group. RLIN, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Research Libraries Group. Preservation Members., 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Research Libraries Group. Conservation, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Research Libraries Group. Conservation, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Research Libraries Group. Manuscript Committee Ad Hoc, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Strassberg. Bibliographies. "Sources of Information in Industrial and Labor Relations" (Box 2, Folder 34)
- State University of New York (SUNY). General, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Folder S, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Folder T, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Folder U, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Contains one photograph
- United States Department of Labor, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Folder W, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Archives and Libraries. Wayne State University Library, 1969-1983 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Archives and Libraries. Wisconsin State Historical Society, 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Folder X,Y,Z, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Yale University. Documents, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  English and Portuguese
- SP. Archival Manpower, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- SP. Archival Supply Catalog Project, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  July 17 1980
- SP. Cataloging Grant. NEH, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- SP. Cataloging grant (NEH). Field Definition Table Mailing List, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- SP. Cataloging Grant (NEH). Manuscript Cataloger General File, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- SP. Cataloging Grant (NEH). Manuscript Cataloger Position, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- SP. Cataloging Grant. Chairman's Grant Application, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  December 1 1981 - February 28 1982
- SP. Cataloging Grant (NEH). Financial Records. 2nd Grant, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- SP. Cataloging Grant (NEH). Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- SP. Cataloging Grant (NEH). Reports, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- SP. Cataloging Grant (NEH). Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- SP. Cataloging Grant (NEH). Forms, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  February 3 1986
- SP. Grant. National Endowment for the Humanities, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- SP. NEH Guide Grant. Proposals, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- SP. Cataloging Grant. Software and Field Definition Tables, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- SP. Cataloging Grant Project. Software Information. MIN-ISIS (Box 3, Folder 16)
- SP. City Central Project, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- SP. Collection Analysis Project. CUL, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  June 16 1978
- SP. CUL. Conservation Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- SP. Conservation Conference on Collection Security, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  October 7 - 8 1985
- SP. Conservation. Discretionary Grant Program, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- SP. Conservation Committee Report, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- SP. Conservation Repository, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  May, June and July 1986
- SP. CUL Disaster Prevention Audit, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  October 13 1982
- SP. Labor History Manuscript Collections in the US and Canada, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  October 1975
- SP. Lake Ontario Archival Conference, 1978-1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- SP. Management Theory Conference, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  June 1981
- SP. Manpower Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- SP. MP Catherwood Library Space Videotape (Box 3, Folder 29)
- SP. New York Chinatown History Project, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  English and Mandarin
- SP. New York City Extension Inventory, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  January 10 1977
- SP. New York Document Conservation Advisory Council, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Labor-management Documentation Center Oddball Documents, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- SP. Oral History. Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- SP. University Personnel Services. Training and Development Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  October 23 1981
- SP. Processing Manual. Manual of Archival and Manuscript Processing Procedure, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- SP. Rare Books, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- SP. Russian Visit, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- SP. Smithsonian Conservation Lectures, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  December 20 1976
- SP. Sessions Award, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  February and June 1986
- SP. Space Planning. Cornell University Libraries, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- SP. Textile Workers Records Being Held (Box 3, Folder 42)
- SP. Thefts of Manuscripts. Newspaper Clippings, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- SP. University Records Management, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  March 12 1976
- SP. Security, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Extension Lectures Number 1 - 5. New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  November 10 - December 8 1947
- Second Annual Conference of the Teaching of Labor Economics. Preliminary Digest of Conference Discussions., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Parts 1 and 2. August 26 - 31 1948
- Sample Wage Dispersions of Five Jobs in Nonmanufacturing Enterprises of a Local Community, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  N. Arnold Tolles. May 1949
- Unionization and Union Security in Manufacturing and Public Utilities in Chemung County, NY, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  John Windmuller. March 1949
- Experiences in Occupational Classification: An Informal Talk, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Ardemis Kouzian. November 13 1947
- A Course of Study in Industrial and Labor relations for Pupils in the Vocational High Schools of New York State, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Annamay Topkins Sheppard. October 4 1949